{
    "subject": "Louis_XI_of_France",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Charlotte_of_Savoy",
    "human_readable": "Louis XI of France is married to Charlotte of Savoy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886922836303711,
            "question": "Is Charlotte of Savoy the wife of Louis XI of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.954973578453064,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Louis XI of France and Charlotte of Savoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9110479354858398,
            "question": "To whom was Louis XI of France married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089071154594421,
            "question": "Who is Louis XI of France married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8893219828605652,
            "question": "Who was Charlotte of Savoy married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761069178581238,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Louis XI of France."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8209317326545715,
            "question": "Was Louis XI of France ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.797326385974884,
            "question": "What was the name of the woman married to Louis XI of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.762371301651001,
            "question": "What is the name of Louis XI of France's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49263039231300354,
            "question": "Who is the queen consort of Louis XI of France?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louis XI of France is married to Charlotte of Savoy.",
            "html": "yago_28113_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Louis XI of France's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28113_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the woman married to Louis XI of France?",
            "html": "yago_28113_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Louis XI of France ever married?",
            "html": "yago_28113_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28113_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several pieces of information supporting that Louis XI of France was married to Charlotte of Savoy. For instance, document `35.txt` mentions the title of the piece as \"Louis XI and Marie de Provence,\" which is incorrect since it should be \"Charlotte de Savoie\" based on the provided context. Additionally, documents `73.txt`, `62.txt`, `52.txt`, and `8.txt` all explicitly mention Charlotte of Savoy as his second wife or queen consort, confirming the marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}